# ROBERTO MAZZARELLO

### Contactáme:



(011) 35640053



rjmazzarello@gmail.com



Bs. As, Argentina.

### Mira mis avances:



github.com/RobertoMaz

- -Movilidad propia
- -Disponibilidad full time

## Trayecioria profesional

Me desempeño hace casi 10 años dentro del rubro de la logística, actualmente soy responsable de la documentación de transporte. Estudio programación con la aspiración de poder expandir mis áreas de desempeño: integrando sistemas y operaciones desde una perspectiva versátil y funcional.

## ÁREAS DE ESPECIALIZACIÓN

- -Análisis de datos
- -Data Entry
- -Git & GitHub
- -JavaScript
- -HTML
- -CSS

### EXPERIENCIA LABORAL

### Analista de documentación

AREA54 S.A | 2015- Actualidad

- -Confeccioné métodos eficientes de gestión de documentación
- -Estandaricé procesos de rendición
- -Trabajé en equipo con un rol de soporte administrativo
- -Brindé atención personalizada a toda la cartera de clientes

#### Operario de depósito

AREA54 S.A | 2013- 2015

- -Gestioné carga y descarga de unidades de transporte
- -Realicé control de inventario
- -Organicé tareas de depósito y de intra-logística
- -Coordiné y supervisé grupos de trabajo de operaciones puntuales

### FORMACIÓN ACADÉMICA

Técnico Superior en programación | 2019 - Actualidad

### OTROS CONOCIMIENTOS

- -Inglés nivel intermedio- Estudiante en "ENGLISH FOR EVERYONE"
- -Manejo de office, sistemas WMS y ERP
- -Manejo de autoelevador
- -Hardware en general

# ROBERTO MAZZARELLO

### Contact me:



(011) 35640053



rjmazzarello@gmail.com



Bs. As, Argentina.

### See my advances:



github.com/RobertoMaz

- -Full availability
- -Native Spanish Speaker

## Career Paih

I have been working for 10 years into the logistics business. Nowadays I am responsible of the transport and distribution documentation. I am studying to be an IT developer and my aspiration is to start working in an IT area. Always contributing with knowledge and versatility.

### AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- -Data Analysis
- -Data Entry
- -Git & GitHub
- -JavaScript
- -HTML
- -CSS

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **Documentation Analyst**

AREA54 S.A | 2015- Now

- -I made efficient methods to manage and organise the information.
- -I standardized surrender processes
- -I gave personalized attention to all the client portfolio

#### Warehouse operator

AREA54 S.A | 2013- 2015

- -Containers charge and discharge
- -Inventory controls
- -I organized and leaded warehousing tasks
- -I managed and supervised groups of work for spot operations

### ACADEMIC TRAINING

Programming technician | 2019 - Now

### EXTRA KNOWLEDGE

- -English Language Student at "ENGLISH FOR EVERYONE"
- -Office, WMS & ERP systems
- -Forklift driving.
- -Hardware in general